Shahrukh Ahmed

Web Developer

About

I am a web-developer with 4+ years of experience. I am currently working largely on the Shopify ecosystem, with focus on building Apps for the Shopify store front. I also have experience working with Shopify stores, creating and editing liquid templates for the store owners. Other than that, I have worked on personal and commercial projects with Django, Vue.js and D3.js.

Contact









Skills

- CSS3
- Shopify API

Shopify

- Javascript
- Svelte.js
- Django
- Vue.js
- D3.js

Work Experience

Freelance Web Development

August 2015 - current

- · Building Public Apps for Shopify Storefront.
- · Creating Educational content teaching HTML, CSS3 and JavaScript.
- Develop, customise and update Shopify e-commerce stores for clients.
- Integrate 3rd party applications that work in tandem with Shopify's core features.
- Customise 3rd party applications to match the UI scheme of the website.
- · Build, test and deploy new and seasonal feature releases.
- · Develop and build custom applications.
- Test the website for cross-browser and device compatibility
- Write documentation and guides for clients to give them an understanding of how to use and implement new or additional features built into the site.
- · Built CRUD applications with Django

Freelance Content Writer

August 2015 - current

I have freelanced for local and international clients. I have written about current-affairs, healthcare, history, entertainment but the bulk of my work has been writing about Climate Change and renewable energy sources. My work typically involves going through dozens of research papers and writing an article that makes a topic easy and clear for the readers to grasp

Yahoo

August 2014 - June 2015

At Yahoo, I worked as a SEM analyst providing account management support to Advertisers. The role primarily included:

- Working with the Account managers and Account Operation Specialists in USA and Canada and providing them with Account Management support.
- Creating, Uploading and maintaining Advertiser Campaigns and various Search Ad formats.
- Finding Account Optimization opportunities to increase advertiser spend and improve account performance
- Quarterly Performance review and competitive insight decks for clients

Education

MBA, PESIT

August 2012 - June 2014

B-Tech, VTU

August 2007 - Dec 2011